let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Who succeeded Qutbuddin Aybak?",
    answer: "Iltutmish",
    options: [
      "Razziya Sultana",
      "Iltutmish",
      "Ghiyasuddin Balban",
      "Jalaluddin Khalji"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following rulers was not the emperor of the Slave Dynasty?",
    answer: "Alauddin Khalji",
    options: [
      "Qutbuddin Aybak",
      "Ghiyasuddin Balban",
      "Iltutmish",
      "Alauddin Khalji"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who <b> Won </b> the first battle of Panipat?",
    answer: "Babur",
    options: [
      "Ibraham Lodi",
      "Akbar",
      "Babur",
      "Jahangir"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who established the rule of <b>Tughluq Dynasty</b>?",
    answer: "Ghiyasuddin Tughluq",
    options: [
      "Ghiyasuddin Tughluq",
      "Muhammad Tughluq",
      "Firuz Shah Tughluq",
      "Mubarak Khan"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who succeeded Babur?",
    answer: "Humayun",
    options: [
      "Akbar",
      "Jahangir",
      "Humayun",
      "Sher Shah Suri"
    ]
  },

 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "During the rule of <b>Aryans</b> India was known as _____________?",
    answer: "Aryavarta",
    options: [
      "Sapta Sindhu",
      "Aryavarta",
      "Hindustan",
      "Bharatvarsha"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "When the <b> Dehli Sultans</b> and <b>Mughals</b> Invaded India which religion spread far and wide?",
    answer: "Islam",
    options: [
      "Islam",
      "Hinduism",
      "Jainism",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the study of <b>Coins</b> Known as?",
    answer: "Numismatics",
    options: [
      "Epigraphy",
      "Numismatics",
      "Paleontology",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Name the ruler who assumed the title of Gangaikonada Chola?",
    answer: "Rajendra Chola",
    options: [
      "Dantiduraga",
      "Dharmapala",
      "Rajaraja Chola",
      "Rajendra Chola"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who was credited for constructing the <b>Kailash Temple</b> and the<b>Ellora Caves</b> in Maharashtra?",
    answer: "Rashtrakutas",
    options: [
      "Chauhans or Chahamanas",
      "Cholas",
      "Rashtrakutas",
      "Palas"
    ]
  },



];